Please Lord, please.
-Clean the cancer inside of her! -We need your help!
What's it say?
Miller Jones.
-Get out. I told you last time. -Come on, now.
Next time, the cops will drag you out.
-Excuse me. -Get out!
Did you need anything else?
Nah, I'm just passing through.
On my way to West Virginia.
I want you to finish it.
You understand?
Yes, sir.
Hell, they having a little revival meetin'.
-God!
-Stubbs! -Stubbs, get out here, man!
Now you remember what I told you?
Dad, no!
Dad!
It's gonna be all right.
Before I found the Holy Ghost...
hiding under my mother's long skirts,
spiders crawling through my dreams...
Praise the Lord.
The Lord looks out for me now!
Helen did, in fact, meet the man she would marry that afternoon.
Bless me, Reverend.
I've heard your word.
Mister, I do appreciate this.
-Sister fucker. -He would do anything to protect her.
Though he wasn't one for praying
It was a sight you didn't end up in the hospital.
Yeah, well, there's a lot of no good sons of bitches out there.
-Happy birthday! -Oh, no.
Nice to meet you too. What you got there?
and thirst...
Preston loved the way people listened to him
But friends...
some of us are better off than others.
Reverend Sykes wept with me.
To show yourself
Do you really want these hands touching you?
No, he's working, making deliveries.
Is it Leroy?
Don't act like you do nothing wrong.
is you figure some way to get rid of it.
living in that poor old woman's house who raised you.
No! No! No!
No, no, no!
lustful acts.
Well, when you say anything,
was just like this...
He was young, but that didn't mean she couldn't make it work.
Shit!
Come on out so we can have us a talk!
I had no choice!
I hate to be the one to tell you this, Sheriff, but your sister...